<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Agora API Example</string>
    <string name="inject">Inject</string>
    <string name="stopinject">StopInject</string>
    <string name="publish">Publish</string>
    <string name="stoppublish">StopPublish</string>
    <string name="url">Url</string>
    <string name="channel_id">Channel ID</string>
    <string name="join">Join</string>
    <string name="leave">Leave</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="permission">Please granted the request permissions</string>
    <string name="earpiece">Earpiece</string>
    <string name="speaker">Speaker</string>
    <string name="openmicrophone">OpenMicrophone</string>
    <string name="closemicrophone">CloseMicrophone</string>
    <string name="sendmeta">Send Metadata</string>
    <string name="quickswitchtips">Make sure you have set up the channel as the comments in the QuickSwitchChannel class say, or you will see a blank.</string>
    <string name="nobroadcaster">There is no broadcaster in the current channel</string>
    <string name="swiptips">You can swipe left and right to switch channels</string>
    <string name="selectrole">Please choose your role</string>
    <string name="broadcaster">BROADCASTER</string>
    <string name="audience">AUDIENCE</string>
    <string name="localvideo">LocalVideo</string>
    <string name="screenshare">ScreenShare</string>
    <string name="alert_no_local_video_message">Local video share will not be accessible.\n Please copy your MP4 video file to %s and change the name as localvideo.mp4.</string>


    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="sdkversion">SDK Version</string>
    <string name="sdkversion1">V%s</string>
    <string name="sent">Sent:%s</string>
    <string name="received">Received:%s</string>


    <string name="joinchannelaudio">This example demonstrates how to use the SDK to make voice calls.</string>
    <string name="joinchannelvideo">This example demonstrates how to use the SDK to make audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="customaudio">This example demonstrates how to automatically collect audio frames and actively push them during a voice call.</string>
    <string name="customremoterender">This example demonstrates how to customize the functions of the remote video stream renderer during audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="processrawdata">This example demonstrates how to obtain raw data through callbacks during audio and video calls, and how to return the data after it has been processed.\nPS:Bare data includes video frames and audio frames</string>
    <string name="pushexternalvideo">This example demonstrates how to capture camera video frames and push them actively during audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="quickswitchchannel">This example demonstrates how to quickly switch channels during audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="rtmpinjection">This example demonstrates how to actively pull and render remote video streams during audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="rtmpstreaming">This example demonstrates how to use the bypass streaming function during an audio and video call.\nPS:Need to build RTMP server.</string>
    <string name="streamencrypt">This example demonstrates how to encrypt and decrypt audio and video frames during audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="switchexternalvideo">This example demonstrates how to actively push video files and how to share screens during audio and video calls.</string>
    <string name="videometadata">This example demonstrates how to send meta information along with video frames during audio and video calls.</string>
</resources>
